Three hundred sixty-six.
Three hundred sixty-seven.
(Amy:)How's it going?
(Sheldon:)How's counting going?
(Sheldon:)When I was in kindergarten...
(Sheldon:)...I recited pi to a thousand places
for the school talent show.
(Sheldon:)- I think I got this.
- Great.
(Sheldon:)Aw, nuts.
(Sheldon:)One.
(Sheldon:)This is preposterous.
(Sheldon:)You're giving me these tasks
because you're afraid...
(Sheldon:)...if you give me anything meaningful
to do, I'll show you up.
(Sheldon:)Yes, that's what I think.
(Amy:)Hey, I've been training in the field
of neurobiology for 12 years.
You've been here three hours and
you spent one of them in the bathroom.
Well, I'm sorry, it takes me a while to get
things going on an unfamiliar toilet.
(Amy:)I've given you the simplest things to do
and you haven't done one of them right.